postupstand.com 2015-03-29

# Learn About Our Privacy Policies | Post-Up Stand Post-Up Stand

Post-Up Stand respects your privacy and the information that you share with us through our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide the following notice to illustrate our online information practices and the choices you have in the way your information is collected and utilized.

### Cookies and Third Party Users

As a third party advertisement vendor, Google uses cookies for ads on Post-Up Stand. Using DART cookies allows Google to serve specific advertisements to users that are based on visits to this site as well as other internet sites that the user has visited.

To opt out of the use of DART cookies by Google, visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Google’s own privacy policies manage the DART cookie system.

Other third party ad servers or networks also have the opportunity to use cookies to track the activities of users on this site in an effort to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements as well as other reasons that may be apparent in their own privacy policies, allowing Post-Up Stand no control over these third party cookie users.

Information that you provide to us through email, phone, website or fax will not be rented or sold to any third party companies.

### Gathering of Personal Information

When you visit us at [www.postupstand.com](http://www.postupstand.com/), the IP address that is used to access the site will be logged. The dates and times of access will be logged as well. This information is used for marketing purposes in an effort to analyze trends, log users movement and collect general information used purely for internal use. Logged IP addresses are not, however, linked to any personally identifiable information.

Any information our customers provide to us is used to accommodate the request stated by the customer at the time of contact such as catalogue requests, order fulfillment or handling of a current/past order. We will use your information to respond to you in regards tothe reason you contacted us via phone, email or fax. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request or to ship an order.

You can change the contact information we have on file such as the contact person, phone number, address and email by logging into your account on our website or by contacting us via email or our toll free number.

Unless a customer contacts us at Post-Up Stand requesting that we do not contact them, we may use your address or email information to direct mail or email in the future to announce specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You can opt out of any future contact from us at any time by sending the request to us at [sales@postupstand.com](mailto:sales@postupstand.com) or 800-935-3534.

### Links to Other Websites

We include on our sites links to third party websites that are relevant to our products and services for added convenience for our customers. We are not held responsible for any privacy policies on websites that are not ours. Please note that we recommend reviewing the privacy policies of sites that are not our own.

### Changes to Post-Up Stand's Privacy Policy

The contents of our privacy policy are subject to change at our discretion.

Feel free to contact Post-Up Stand with any questions regarding our privacy policy at [sales@postupstand.com](mailto:sales@postupstand.com) or 1-800-935-3534.
